Guide to the Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File Additional records, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: An introduction to Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
    By Policyholders Service Bureau. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Selected References on Wage Incentives, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
    By Industrial Relations Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Incentive Wage Systems, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
    By Robert L. Aronson. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Our Six Years With the Rucker Plan, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
    By Daniel Pohlman. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Industrial relations Problems Arising Under War Production, Publication (Box 28, Folder 7)
    By Florence, Peterson. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Standards of Wage Determination, Publication (Box 28, Folder 8)
    By Paul Bullock. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: What's Wtong With Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 28, Folder 8)
    By Research Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Job Evaluation: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography, Publication (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Job Rating Plans Used by NEMA Member Companies, Publication (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Personel Management Series 4, Publication (Box 28, Folder 8)
    By Job Evaluation: A Practical Guide. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A Labor Union Manual on Job Evaluation, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
    By William Gomberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Industrial Job Evaluation Systems, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
    With Annotated Bibliography. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Job Evaluation: A Selected, Annotated Bibliography, Publication (Box 28, Folder 9)
    By Industrial Relations Section. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Systematic Wage Administration in the Southern California Aircraft Industry, Publication (Box 28, Folder 10)
    By Robert Gray. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Industrial Job Evaluation Systems, Publication (Box 28, Folder 10)
    By War Manpower Commission. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Wage and Salary Administration, Publication (Box 28, Folder 10)
    By Verbatim Conference Record. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Pay Differentials for Night Work Provided Under Union Agreements, Publication (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Job Rating, Publication (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Accelerated Vocational Training for Adults, Publication (Box 28, Folder 12)
    By Victor Martin. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary Administration, Publication (Box 28, Folder 13)
    By John Coyle. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Wages and Salaries, Publication (Box 28, Folder 13)
    By J. E. Genders; N. J. Urwin. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Vocational Rehabilitaion of Michigan's Disabled Manpower, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Vocational Teaching, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Pre-Induction Vocational Training in Aircraft Manitenance, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Vocational Education and Federal Policy, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
    By Sar A. Levitan. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Learning for Living, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
    By The State Board of Control for Vocational Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Pre-Induction Training in Vocational Schools Vocational Departments and Trade Schools, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
    By US War Department and the US Office of Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Pre-Induction Vocational Training in Machine Shop Practice, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Pre-Induction Vocational Training in Electrical Signal Communication, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
    By US War Department and US Office of Education. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Pre-Induction Voaational Training in Auto Mechanics, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Vocational Training and Employment of Youth, Publication (Box 28, Folder 14)
    By Selden Manefe; John Webb. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Problems of reempliyment and Retaining of Manpower During the Transition from War to Peace, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Jobs for the War Disabled, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
    By Ametican Veterans Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Sickness Benefits and Group Purchase of Medical Care for Industrial Employees, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Industry Reports on Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Adjustment of Negro Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
    By Julius Thomas. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Employment of Male World War II Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Industry reports to Veterans on Jobs, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 8: Rehiring Your Company's Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
    By Research Institute of America. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Employment of the Handicapped Veteran, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Reemployment of War Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 11: You and Joe and his Job, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 12: Federal Benefits for Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 13: Reemployment of Veterans Under Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Item 14: Employment of Ex-Servicemen in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Supplumental Study and Report. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Employment of Ex-Servicemen in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Supplemental Study No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: What the Solder Thinks, Publication (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Post-War Plans of the Solder. Item is in English.
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: National UAW-CIO War Veterans Conference, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Reemployment of Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Rehabilitation and Training for Postwar Employment, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Apprenticeship and on-the-job Training for Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Solders' Plans for Farming After They Leave the Army, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: Responsibilities of the Employer in the Employment of Veterans, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Item 7: Seniority, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
    An analysis of the Problems that face Industry and the Government as Veterans Return for their Jobs. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: reemployment of Ex-Servicemen in the Iron and Steel Industry, Publication (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Crisis of the Cities: A Coporate Concern, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: IDEA Exchange on Solving Urban Problems, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
    By Employee Communication Operation of Employee Relations. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Urban Problems and the Private Sector, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
    By Saul Wallen. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: idea Exchange on Solving Urban Problems, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: Who "Riots" and Why?, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
    By Karl Flaming. Black and White Perspectives in Milwaukee. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Detroit Riot A Profile of 500 Prisoners, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: The Private Sector's Role in the Urban Crisis, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
    By William Zisch. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: How General Electric People are Trying to Help, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Item 9: Spacial Aspects of Urban labor Markets, Publication (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Box 28, Folder (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Quality of the Future, Publication (Box 28, Folder 18)
    By George Harrar. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Violence in the City -- An End or a Beginning?, Publication (Box 28, Folder 18)
    By Governor's Commission on the Los Angeles Riots. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Time to Listen.. A Time to Act, Publication (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Voices from the Ghettos of the Nation's Cities. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The 801st Man: or A Man for the 21st Century, Publication (Box 28, Folder 18)
    By F. J. Borch. Item is in English.
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Manpower and Wage Cost Trends:The Wage-Price Guideposts, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: From "Guideposts" to " Guidelines" to "?", Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Wage-Price Policies: Some Lessons from Abroad, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Lloyd Ulman. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Some Economic Forces at Work in the Changing Picture in Industrial relations, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Frank Highton. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Labor Developments and Problems in an Affluent Society, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    1967-1968. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Collective Bargaining and Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: The Wage, Productivity, Price Issue, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By John W. Kendrisk. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Wage Escalation and Wage Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Joseph Garbarino. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Wage Escalation and Wage Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: What it is, Where it comes from, ho it is measured, How it is shared, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Productivity. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Productivity, Pay and Prices, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Arthur Upgren. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The National Wage Policy:, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Abraham Gitlow. Antecedents and Application. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Escalation, Productivity, Wages and Costs -- Do the Figures Tell the Story?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Ewan Clague. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Wage Escalation and Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Jules Backman. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Argument for Creeping Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Inflation: Rob us All, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Labor Gets 83.2c out of Every Dollar!, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Congressional Record. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Profits, Productivity and Personnel Administration -- A Look at the Future, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By J. W. Oram. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: War Price relations in th Basic Steel Industry in the Post War Period, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Albert Rees. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Inflation - Cause and Cure, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 21: Sidney Hillman Foundation Lectures, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Arthur Goldberg; B. C Roberts. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Labor, Big Business and Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: The Impacts of Unions on the Level of Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Clark Kerr. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Facts on the Line, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Productivity, Wages and Jobs at Home and Abroad, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By 14th Annual IRC Labor Conference. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Economics ad Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 27: The Productivity Factor in Wage Adjustments, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Princeton University. Selected references. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Slow Inflation: AN Inescapable Cost of Maximum Growth Rate, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 29: Let's Set the Record Straight on Unemployment Inflation Profits-Prices Export-Imports, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By David McDonald. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Another Look at Wage Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Robert Tyson. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Wages Prices Profits Productivity, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Item 32: Wage Theory, Wage Rates and Productivity, Publication (Box 29, Folder 1)
    By Joseph Taggart; Cliffort Clark. Item is in English.
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Impacts of Unions on the Level of Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Labor, Big Business and Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Labor Management Relations and Wages, Prices and Politics, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    By Arhur Goldberg; B.C Roberts. 1958-1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: When Wage Inflation Causes Price Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Administered Prices and Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Some Public Policy Issues. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Wages as a Factor in Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    By Joseph Beirne. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The People vs the Profiteers, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    By Education and Research Departments, IUE-AFL-CIO. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Billion Dollar Bundle, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    By Roger Blough. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Relationship of Prices to Economic Stability and Growth, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    By Economists from Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Unions, Anti-Trust Laws and Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 2)
    By Frederick Meyers. Item is in English.
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Wage and Price Controls: A Failure in History, Theory and Practice, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Wages Councils and Income Policy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    By Robert Banks. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Guidepost Revisited: A Look at the 1966 Model, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Guidepost 'Escalator' Would Escalate Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: The Impact of National Wage Policies, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
    By Everett Kassalow. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: 1976 Collective Bargaining Negotiations: A Background Paper, Publication (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Another Look at the "Wage Guideposts", Publication (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Inflation Control Productivity and Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    By Marvin Kosters; Markley Roberts; Robert Bassett; Jerome Rosow; Bruce Thrasher. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Productivity and Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    By Selected References. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Guidelines and the Inflation Problem, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: A Model of Work Effort and Productive Consumption, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    By Malcom Cohen; Frank Stafford. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Short-Run Wage-Price Mechanism in U.S. Manufacturing, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    By Calvin Siebert; Mahmood Zaidi. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Productivity and related Factors in a Post-Freeze Wage Policy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Population Growth and the Growth of Output and Per Capita Income in a Product Function Framework, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    By Anthony P. Thirwall. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Use of Productivity in Bargaining and Some Perspectives on the 5.5% Pay Guide, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Statement with Respect to HR 17880, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    By Leonard Woodcock. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Earnings, Prices, Labor Costs, Productivity, G.N.P, Foreign Trade, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: The Future of American Wage Controls, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
    By Daniel Mitchell. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Productivity and the Activities of the Council, Publication (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Restoring Management Control of Wages and Hours, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
    By Allen Rucker. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Share of Production Wage Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: A Bonus System of Rewarding Labor, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
    By H. L. Gantt. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Economic Effects of Steady Employment and Earnings, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
    By jack Chernick. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Utilization of Labor, Publication (Box 29, Folder 6)
    By Gantt, H. L. Item is in English.
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Inflation, Unions and Wage Policy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: The Impact of Unionism on Wage-Income Ratios in the Manufacturing Sector of the Economy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
    By Norman Simler. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Foreign Competition and Steel Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Union Impact on Salaried Personnel, Publication (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Can Unions Raise Spendable Income or Can Unions Influence Wages - A re-Statement, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
    By Edward Shaw; Edwin Miller. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Foreign Competition and Steel Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Wage Theories, Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Profits and Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
    By Anna Rochester. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: labor Policy and the Business Cycle, Publication (Box 29, Folder 9)
    By Sidney Sufrin. Item is in English.
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Wage Stabilization and Emergency Disputes, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: The Present Crisit in Price and Wage Controls, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Special Report by the Staff. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Settlement of Labor Disputes and Wage Stabilization, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Wage Control, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By William Chartener. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The National Wage Stabilization Code, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Wage Stabilization General Orders and Interpretations, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Wage report to the President on the Wartime Relatioship of Wages to the Cost of Living, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: The Lessons of Price and Wage Controls, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Arthur Ross. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Government Wage Restraints: Their Limits and Uses in a Mobilized Economy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Ending Price-Wage Controls, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By The Program Committee. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Problems and Policies of Dispute Settlement and Wage Stabilization During World War II, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 12: Problems in Business and industrial Mobilization, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Carroll Daugherty. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Wage Stabilization in a Defense Economy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 14: Salary Freezing and How it Works, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 15: The 'Double Standard' of Stabilization, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By C. L. Austin. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Productivity and Wage Control, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 17: Interplant Wage Rothbaum, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Harold Ross; Melvin Rothbaum. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Wage Stabilization Policy of the National War Labor Board, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Philip Arnow. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Extract Relating Specifically to Wage and Salary Stabilization, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 20: Economic Controls in our National Emergency, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 21: Providing for the Continued Stabilization of the National Economy During the Transition from War to Peace, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Executive Order 9697. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Health, Welfare and Pension Programs Under Wage Stabilization, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 23: What's Ahead for Wage Stabilization?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Nathan Feinsinger. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Some Views on Current Industrial Relations Problems, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Item 25: Wage Stabilization and Inflation, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By L. R. Boulware. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Price and Wage Controls, Publication (Box 29, Folder 10)
    By Research for Economic Development. Item is in English.
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Nunn-Bush Plan, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
    By H. L. Nunn. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Wage Negotiations in Wartime, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Statistical Wage Stabilization, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
    By Robert Myers; Harry Ober. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: How Feasible is an Annual Wage for Labor?, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Stable Employment and Flexible Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
    By Charles A. Myers. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Wage Stabilization and Adjustment Policies of the National War Labor Board, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Pay Increases Under Wage and Salary Stability, Publication (Box 29, Folder 11)
    By Leo M. Cherne. Item is in English.
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Paying Employees by Check, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Wage Systems in Industry, Publication (Box 29, Folder 12)
    By J. C. Pierre. Item is in English.
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Nathan Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Development and Recommendation of a Departmen of defense Wage Policy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Information about the Government's Wage-Price Policy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: Wage Policy in our Expanding Economy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Wage and Industrial Progress, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
    By George Taylor. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A National Wage Policy, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
    By Robert Nathan; Oscar Gass. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Facts Versus the Nathan Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
    By Ralph Robey. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Private Wage Bargains and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Critical Appraisal of the Nathan Report, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Wage-Price Policy and Employment, Publication (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Wages in Manufacturing Industry in the United States, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Stabilized Wage Rates and Job Standards, Publication (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Box 29, Folder (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A Story About 50,000 New York Women, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: The High Cost of Low Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Let our People Live, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Joseph Gaer. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Minimum Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Frank Huddle. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: On the Home Front with Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Substandard Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Abraham Joel Tobias. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
    By Radio Forum. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Suggested Language for State, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 9: The Guaranteed Minimum Weekly Wage, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Item 10: Minimum Wages, Publication (Box 29, Folder 15)